JULIAN REZA ERWANDI

Batam, Indonesia | +6282169006397 | jrerwandi@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/jr-erwandi | github.com/jrerwandi

OBJECTIVE

I am a Software Engineer at PT TEC Indonesia. I completed my Bachelor of Robotics Engineering from Batam State Polytechnic in 2022. While in college, I was a member of the Humanoid Robot Research Group (BarelangFC) as a programmer team. I am interested in programming, especially **desktop applications**, **robotics**, **computer vision**, **microcontrollers** and **artificial intelligence**. I like to try new things and try to keep growing. You can find my portfolio through my **Github Repository** or **Personal Web Page** [link].

EXPERIENCE

- PT. TEC INDONESIA | | BATAM, KEPULAUAN RIAU, INDONESIA Software Engineer (July 2022 - Present)
- PT. KUANTUM GABE INTEGRITAS | | BATAM, KEPULAUAN RIAU, INDONESIA Programmer (Internship) (March 2022 – July 2022)
 - Worked on a project monitoring temperature and humidity. In this project I am responsible for microcontroller programming using ATMEGA2560 + ESP32 as MQTT client.
 - Worked on a project monitoring temperature and humidity. In this project I am responsible for microcontroller programming using ATMEGA2560 + Ethernet W5500 as MQTT client.
 - Worked on a project monitoring temperature and humidity. In this project I am responsible for microcontroller programming using STM32F103C8T6 + Ethernet W5500 as MQTT client and save config to EEPROM
 - worked on a project outgoing tester. in this project I am responsible for UI software, run .sql script in VB.Net for create database programmatically.
 - Develop software serial tester (VB.Net + SQLite)
- **HUMANOID ROBOT RESEARCH GROUP (BARELANG FC)** | BATAM, KEPULAUAN RIAU, INDONESIA *Programmer* (2018 2022)
 - As a programmer team member, I am responsible for Robot programming, Robot localization based on C, C++, C#,
 Python, Inverse Kinematics and Computer Vision.

EDUCATION

• BATAM STATE POLYTECHNIC | BATAM, KEPULAUAN RIAU, INDONESIA

Robotics Engineering (August 2018 – August 2022)

- **GPA** : 3.8 [transcript]
- Final Project : Differential evolution for solving inverse kinematics problem in the upper body of an adult-sized humanoid robot [link]
- SMAN 2 TEMBILAHAN | INDRAGIRI HILIR, RIAU, INDONESIA

IPA (2015 - 2018)

SKILLS

- Programming base on C, C++, C#, VB.net, Python
- Microcontrollers Programming
- Computer Vision
- Internet of Things (IoT)
- SQL
- Research and Development
- PLC

CERTIFICATIONS

PLC | Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP) [link]

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Some of my achievements so far are as follows [link].